<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Explore Romania</string>

    <string name="tab_must_see">must see</string>
    <string name="tab_cities">cities</string>
    <string name="tab_castles">castles</string>
    <string name="tab_nature">nature</string>
    <string name="bran_city">Bran</string>
    <string name="sinaia_city">Sinaia</string>
    <string name="hunedoara_city">Hunedoara</string>
    <string name="fagaras_city">Făgăraș</string>
    <string name="rasnov_city">Râșnov</string>
    <string name="romania_country">Romania</string>
    <string name="peles_castle_name">Peles Castle</string>
    <string name="peles_castle_desc">Peleș Castle is a Neo-Renaissance castle in the Carpathian Mountains, near Sinaia, in Prahova County, Romania, on an existing medieval route linking Transylvania and Wallachia, built between 1873 and 1914. Its inauguration was held in 1883. It was constructed for King Carol I.</string>
    <string name="bran_castle_name">Bran Castle</string>
    <string name="bran_castle_desc">Bran Castle is a castle in Bran, 25 kilometres southwest of Brașov. It is a national monument and landmark in Romania. The fortress is on the Transylvanian side of the historical border with Wallachia, on road DN73.</string>
    <string name="corvine_castle_name">Corvins\' Castle</string>
    <string name="corvine_castle_desc">Corvin Castle, also known as Hunyadi Castle or Hunedoara Castle, is a Gothic-Renaissance castle in Hunedoara, Romania. It is one of the largest castles in Europe and figures in a list of the Seven Wonders of Romania</string>
    <string name="fagaras_castle_name">Făgăraș Citadel</string>
    <string name="fagaras_castle_desc">Făgăraș Citadel is a historic monument in Făgăraș, Romania. Its construction started in 1310 on the grounds of an older fortification made of wood and dirt.</string>
    <string name="rasnov_castle_name">Râșnov Fortress</string>
    <string name="rasnov_castle_desc">Râșnov Fortress is a historic monument and landmark in Romania. It is situated in Râşnov, Brașov County, in the immediate vicinity of Brașov. The fortress was built as part of a defence system for the Transylvanian villages exposed to outside invasions.</string>
    <string name="turda_city">Turda</string>
    <string name="bucharest_city_name">Bucharest</string>
    <string name="salina_mine_name">Salina Turda</string>
    <string name="salina_mine_desc">Salina Turda is a salt mine in the Durgău-Valea Sărată area of Turda, the second largest city in Cluj County, northwest Romania. Opened for tourists in 1992, the Salina Turda mine was visited by about 618,000 Romanian and foreign tourists in 2017.</string>
    <string name="parl_palace_name">Palace of Parliament</string>
    <string name="parl_palace_desc">The Palace of the Parliament is the seat of the Parliament of Romania, located atop Dealul Spirii in Bucharest, the national capital. The Palace has a height of 84 metres, a floor area of 365,000 square metres and a volume of 2,550,000 cubic metres.</string>
    <string name="trans_road_name">Transfăgărășan</string>
    <string name="trans_road_desc">The Transfăgărășan or DN7C is a paved mountain road crossing the southern section of the Carpathian Mountains of Romania. It has national-road ranking and is the second-highest paved road in the country after the Transalpina.</string>
    <string name="balea_lake_name">Bâlea Lake</string>
    <string name="balea_lake_desc">Bâlea Lake is a glacier lake situated at 2,034 m of altitude in the Făgăraș Mountains, in central Romania, in Cârțișoara, Sibiu County. There are two chalets opened all the year round, a meteorological station and a mountain rescue station.</string>
    <string name="timisoara_city_name">Timisoara</string>
    <string name="sibiu_city_name">Sibiu</string>
    <string name="cluj_city_name">Cluj</string>
    <string name="brasov_city_name">Brasov</string>
    <string name="sighisoara_city_name">Sighisoara</string>
    <string name="iasi_city_name">Iasi</string>
    <string name="constanta_city_name">Constanta</string>
    <string name="bucharest_city_desc">Calling all visiting artists and musicians – Bucharest is the capital of Romania and has nothing to do with Budapest, the Hungarian capital. This being cleared, let’s see what Bucharest has to offer its visitors.</string>
    <string name="timisoara_city_desc">Located in western Romania, in the Banat region, Timisoara is a cosmopolitan metropolis with a distinct university vibe and lovely architecture to marvel at. It is also the symbol of Romania’s democracy and one of the most beloved cities in the country.</string>
    <string name="sibiu_city_desc">Located in the charming Transylvania region, the medieval city of Sibiu is the Gothic fairy tale of Romania. After enjoying a year in the spotlight in 2007, when it was elected the cultural capital of Europe, Sibiu became one of the country’s most sought after destinations.</string>
    <string name="cluj_city_desc">The second largest city in Romania, Cluj-Napoca, or simply Cluj, is an ancient metropolis with a young soul, located right in the heart of Transylvania. With a rich history, plenty of medieval castles, fortified churches, museums, and a highly artistic sense, it’s no wonder Cluj is the poetic hub of Romania, a very elegant and romantic one.</string>
    <string name="brasov_city_desc">Surrounded by mountains and filled with fairytale-like architecture, Brasov is another delightful medieval chapter of Transylvania.</string>
    <string name="sighisoara_city_desc">Part of UNESCO’s prestigious list, Sighisoara is one of the prettiest and best preserved inhabited citadels in Europe. Home to the notorious Vlad the Impaler, the character who inspired Bram Stoker’ Dracula, the city seems straight out of a mythical bygone realm, with impossibly narrow alleyways, surreal candy-colored houses, and lots of frightening legends entwined between its fabled towers and ramparts.</string>
    <string name="iasi_city_desc">In the beautiful city of Iasi, every stone, museum, monastery, park, or memorial house talks about the nation’s literary past. Located in northeastern Romania, the former capital of Moldavia stretches over seven rolling hills (just like Rome), offering visitors not just a valuable history lesson, but also wonderful landscapes at every turn.</string>
    <string name="constanta_city_desc">Situated in southeastern Romania, on the Black Sea shore, Constanta is the largest port and coastal city in the country. Founded under the name of Tomis, by the Greek colonists from Miletus in the VII century BC, this is a unique blend of Roman, Greek, and Turkish influences, and the place where some of the most valuable archaeological sites on the Romanian territory can be found.</string>
    <string name="carass_city_name">Caras Severin</string>
    <string name="bigar_waterfall_name">Bigar Cascade Falls</string>
    <string name="bigar_waterfall_desc">Located in the nature reserve in Anina Mountains, the amazing waterfall is indeed a unique one. The water falls from a cliff, which is covered with moss. It is said to be the most beautiful waterfall in the country. The underground spring streams from the cave above and then falls into Minis River.</string>
    <string name="ana_lake_name">Lake Saint Ann</string>
    <string name="ana_lake_desc">Lake Sfânta Ana is the only crater lake in Romania located in the volcanic crater of the volcano named Ciomatu Mare of the Eastern Carpathians, near Tușnad in the Natural Reserve of Mohoș, Harghita County, Romania.</string>
    <string name="delta_river_name">Danube Delta</string>
    <string name="delta_river_desc">The Danube Delta is the second largest river delta in Europe, after the Volga Delta, and is the best preserved on the continent. The greater part of the Danube Delta lies in Romania, with a small part in Ukraine. Its approximate surface area is 4,152 km², of which 3,446 km² is in Romania.</string>
    <string name="red_lake_name">Red Lake</string>
    <string name="red_lake_desc">Red Lake is a natural dam lake formed following the collapse of a slope due to the earthquake of January 23, 1838 at 18:45, 6.9 magnitude, VIII intensity, at the foot of Hasmasul Mare Mountain, near the Bicaz Gorge, at a distance of 26 km from Gheorgheni, in Harghita County</string>
    <string name="sight_image">Sight image</string>
</resources>
